{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A currency chest book should be retained for _______ complete ﬁnancial years after it ceases to be in use",
      "correct_answer": "three",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        " one",
        " two",
        "four"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The Form number used for currency chest book is",
      "correct_answer": "TR37",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "TR30",
        "TR10",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Whose oﬃcers conduct the veriﬁcation of the balance in a chest in the sole custody of the Bank?. ",
      "correct_answer": "Reserve Bank of India",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        " State Bank of India Head oﬃce",
        " ICICI Bank ",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Schedule for Provident fund deductions shall be prepared in",
      "correct_answer": "TR104",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "TR7A ",
        "TR37",
        "TR42"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A ________ Register will be maintained by the drawing oﬃcers in Form 9A prescribed in Volume II of Kerala Financial Code.",
      "correct_answer": "Increment Register",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Contingent Register",
        "Miscellaneous Register",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Absentee statement shall be prepared in Form Number _________",
      "correct_answer": "TR52",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "TR42",
        "TR37",
        "TR7A"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The form prescribed for last pay certiﬁcate should be prepared in which of the following appendices.",
      "correct_answer": "Appendix 12",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Appendix 2",
        " Appendix 10 ",
        "None of these "
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A Government servant who retires on pension is required to produce _______ before he can draw his pension for the ﬁrst time.",
      "correct_answer": "Last pay certiﬁcate",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Salary certiﬁcate",
        "Non creamy layer certiﬁcate",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who is the authority to draw sent bills of Government primary schools in their jurisdiction?",
      "correct_answer": "The Assistant Educational Oﬃcer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The Headmaster",
        "DPI",
        "The Junior Superintendent"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Permanent advance bill form is in _________",
      "correct_answer": " TR 42",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "TR 37",
        "TR 56",
        "None of these"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
